<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Wheelspedia</string>
    <string name="title_activity_toyota">TOYOTA</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"

        "Resting elevation.\n\n"

        "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation "
        "that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting "
        "elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

        "Component elevations.\n\n"

        "The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation "
        "does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n"
        "Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth "
        "of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n"

        "Responsive elevation and dynamic elevation offsets.\n\n"

        "Some component types have responsive elevation, meaning they change elevation in response "
        "to user input (e.g., normal, focused, and pressed) or system events. These elevation "
        "changes are consistently implemented using dynamic elevation offsets.\n"
        "Dynamic elevation offsets are the goal elevation that a component moves towards, relative "
        "to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent "
        "across actions and component types. For example, all components that lift on press have "
        "the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n"
        "Once the input event is completed or cancelled, the component will return to its resting "
        "elevation.\n\n"

        "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_suzuki">suzuki</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>
    <string name="title_activity_hyundai">hyundai</string>
    <string name="title_activity_tata">tata</string>
    <string name="title_activity_kia">kia</string>
    <string name="under_global_ncap_s_recently_revised_crash_test_protocols_for_its_safer_cars_for_india_programme_the_uk_based_vehicle_safety_watchdog_mandates_esc_as_a_standalone_option_as_well_as_an_assessment_on_side_impact_and_pedestrian_protection_tests_for_a_car_to_be_evaluated_for_a_5_star_safety_rating_hyundai_is_also_considering_getting_the_exter_crash_tested_under_the_upcoming_bharat_new_car_assessment_programme_crash_regime_which_is_likely_to_be_introduced_in_the_country_from_october_1_2023_as_per_the_draft_bharat_ncap_protocol_issued_by_the_ministry_of_road_transport_amp_highways_morth_the_india_specific_voluntary_crash_tests_take_references_from_the_revised_july_2022_to_december_2025_global_ncap_protocols_and_demand_esc_pole_side_impact_pedestrian_protection_as_well_as_seat_belt_reminders_as_the_qualifying_safety_requirements_for_a_car_to_aim_for_five_stars_in_its_tests_hyundai_india_says_it_s_eyeing_a_good_ncap_rating_for_the_exter_safety_has_been_a_key_focus_area_with_the_exter_and_with_all_the_structural_changes_that_we_have_done_along_with_offering_six_airbags_as_standard_and_esc_right_from_the_base_trim_we_will_have_a_good_ncap_rating_tarun_garg_chief_operating_officer_at_hmil_told_our_sister_publication_autocar_professional_for_global_ncap_safety_tests_esc_has_become_an_important_requirement_to_have_a_good_star_rating_the_new_protocols_state_that_esc_should_be_available_as_standard_in_the_bestselling_variants_or_should_be_available_in_equal_numbers_in_other_variants_hyundai_has_done_just_that_by_offering_esc_as_standard_on_most_variants_and_as_an_option_on_the_base_variant_exhaustive_list_of_safety_features_while_hyundai_india_has_received_flak_in_the_past_for_some_of_its_popular_models_like_the_midsize_creta_suv_scoring_only_three_stars_in_the_gncap_crash_tests_along_with_an_unstable_body_shell_remark_it_is_now_looking_to_make_amends_the_exter_gets_a_mix_of_active_and_passive_safety_kit_on_board_including_six_airbags_seat_belt_reminders_and_three_point_seat_belts_for_all_seats_across_all_five_trims_it_additionally_gets_the_option_of_advanced_safety_features_including_esc_vehicle_stability_management_vsm_hill_assist_control_hac_isofix_child_seat_mounts_a_direct_tpms_tyre_pressure_monitoring_system_along_with_a_dual_facing_dashboard_camera_that_records_cabin_as_well_as_outside_footage_while_hyundai_motor_india_is_confident_of_a_good_crash_test_rating_for_its_latest_set_of_wheels_only_a_global_ncap_or_bharat_ncap_crash_test_result_will_determine_if_the_carmaker_is_walking_the_safety_talk"><![CDATA[Under Global NCAP\'s recently revised crash test protocols for its Safer Cars for India programme, the UK-based vehicle safety watchdog mandates ESC as a standalone option, as well as an assessment on side-impact and pedestrian-protection tests, for a car to be evaluated for a 5-star safety rating. Hyundai is also considering getting the Exter crash tested under the upcoming Bharat New Car Assessment Programme crash regime, which is likely to be introduced in the country from October 1, 2023. As per the draft Bharat NCAP protocol issued by the Ministry of Road Transport & Highways (MoRTH), the India-specific voluntary crash tests take references from the revised (July 2022 to December 2025) Global NCAP protocols, and demand ESC, pole side impact, pedestrian protection as well as seat-belt reminders as the qualifying safety requirements for a car to aim for five stars in its tests. Hyundai India says it’s eyeing a \'good NCAP rating\' for the Exter. Safety has been a key focus area with the Exter, and with all the structural changes that we have done along with offering six airbags as standard, and ESC right from the base trim, we will have a good NCAP rating,Tarun Garg, chief operating officer at HMIL, told our sister publication Autocar Professional. For Global NCAP safety tests, ESC has become an important requirement to have a good star rating. The new protocols state that ESC should be available as standard in the bestselling variants or should be available in equal numbers in other variants. Hyundai has done just that by offering ESC as standard on most variants and as an option on the base variant. Exhaustive list of safety features While Hyundai India has received flak in the past for some of its popular models, like the midsize Creta SUV scoring only three stars in the GNCAP crash tests, along with an \'unstable body shell\' remark, it is now looking to make amends. The Exter gets a mix of active- and passive-safety kit on board, including six airbags, seat-belt reminders and three-point seat belts for all seats, across all five trims. It additionally gets the option of advanced safety features, including ESC, vehicle stability management (VSM), hill-assist control (HAC), ISOFIX child-seat mounts, a direct TPMS (tyre pressure monitoring system), along with a dual-facing dashboard camera that records cabin as well as outside footage. While Hyundai Motor India is confident of a good crash test rating for its latest set of wheels, only a Global NCAP or Bharat NCAP crash test result will determine if the carmaker is walking the safety talk.]]></string>
    <string name="we_are_putting_batteries_in_everything_from_scooters_to_suvs_and_calling_them_green_but_batteries_have_their_own_environmental_problems_fossil_fuels_are_the_worst_it_wouldn_t_be_a_stretch_to_blame_them_and_the_industries_they_have_enabled_for_pretty_much_the_entirety_of_our_spiraling_climate_meltdown_from_this_point_of_view_almost_anything_is_better_we_need_to_ditch_coal_and_oil_asap_no_matter_what_it_takes_at_the_same_time_we_should_be_taking_a_long_look_at_the_problems_with_batteries_battery_fires_the_use_of_child_labor_to_mine_rare_minerals_etc_so_they_don_t_become_yet_another_disaster_lithium_ion_batteries_especially_those_powering_most_e_bikes_and_scooters_need_to_improve_drastically_in_addition_to_long_charging_times_the_most_pressing_concern_is_catching_fire_lithium_ion_batteries_have_already_sparked_22_fires_that_caused_36_injuries_and_two_deaths_in_new_york_city_this_year_charlie_welch_ceo_and_co_founder_of_zapbatt_told_lifewire_via_email_ev_battery_life_batteries_are_fueling_ev_growth_from_giant_suvs_to_humble_electric_bikes_we_focus_on_the_good_aspects_that_they_can_be_recharged_there_are_no_local_emissions_electric_motors_are_silent_etc_but_we_also_ignore_the_problems_first_producing_batteries_has_a_significant_environmental_and_human_impact_until_a_battery_can_be_made_sustainably_from_both_a_human_and_environmental_perspective_the_growth_of_battery_use_won_t_be_sustainable_too_commonly_batteries_are_made_with_cobalt_which_is_a_highly_volatile_and_unsustainable_mineral_to_source_there_are_several_cobalt_mines_in_africa_particularly_in_the_congo_where_child_labor_is_all_too_common_ashish_gadnis_ceo_of_sustainable_sourcing_company_banqu_told_lifewire_via_email_and_even_after_manufacturing_the_lifecycle_of_a_battery_is_shorter_than_you_might_expect_because_many_e_bike_and_scooter_oems_use_cheaper_batteries_with_shorter_life_cycles_there_is_unfortunately_a_growing_mountain_of_e_waste_with_micro_mobility_operators_swapping_a_tsunami_of_conventional_lithium_ion_batteries_on_e_bikes_and_e_scooters_and_with_few_recycling_options_available_at_present_we_are_well_on_our_way_to_building_a_massive_battery_graveyard_and_squandering_the_rare_earth_minerals_used_to_manufacture_them_says_zappbat_s_welch_ev_battery_recycling_then_too_recycling_itself_has_an_impact_oftentimes_we_think_that_encouraging_recycling_is_the_catch_all_solution_to_making_the_material_more_sustainable_but_unfortunately_it_isn_t_recycling_programs_are_often_happening_at_these_very_mines_where_child_labor_is_rampant_so_until_a_battery_can_be_made_sustainably_from_both_a_human_and_environmental_perspective_the_growth_of_battery_use_won_t_be_sustainable_says_gadnis_a_worker_in_protective_clothing_loading_vehicle_batteries_into_a_bin_at_a_recycling_plant_monty_rakusen_getty_images_and_that_s_if_you_can_even_recycle_them_at_the_end_of_their_lives_batteries_can_become_pretty_toxic_many_batteries_and_solar_panel_parts_are_not_recyclable_which_obviously_increases_our_waste_generation_improperly_disposed_of_batteries_can_also_cause_soil_water_and_air_pollution_caio_bersot_energy_analyst_at_energyrates_ca_told_lifewire_via_email_alternatives_like_hydrogen_fuel_cells_one_other_option_is_hydrogen_it_s_not_perfect_of_course_and_it_would_require_a_distribution_network_similar_in_principle_to_that_of_gasoline_rather_than_using_our_existing_electricity_grid_but_the_advantage_is_that_refueling_can_be_faster_than_charging_a_car_you_can_fill_up_in_just_four_minutes_and_the_car_still_runs_on_electricity_and_produces_only_water_as_waste_hydrogen_fuel_cells_although_a_bit_more_expensive_than_electric_vehicles_have_a_smaller_impact_on_the_environment_as_they_only_emit_water_when_powered_with_hydrogen_however_all_vehicles_regardless_of_how_they_are_powered_will_require_multiple_resources_both_natural_and_manufactured_says_bersot_closeup_on_the_back_of_a_car_that_has_an_emblem_that_reads_hydrogen_fuel_cell_gchutka_getty_images_but_hydrogen_is_also_like_batteries_less_energy_dense_than_gas_so_you_need_to_carry_more_of_it_and_store_it_at_high_pressure_the_real_problem_is_that_we_have_built_some_societies_around_individual_vehicles_for_both_extended_and_short_distance_use_those_vehicles_are_far_too_big_a_hangover_from_the_plentiful_energy_of_cheap_gasoline_long_distance_journeys_are_best_made_on_electric_trains_that_don_t_run_on_batteries_while_shorter_trips_can_be_made_by_bike_or_public_city_transport_again_all_of_which_can_be_battery_free">We are putting batteries in everything, from scooters to SUVs, and calling them green. But batteries have their own environmental problems. Fossil fuels are the worst. It wouldn\'t be a stretch to blame them and the industries they have enabled for pretty much the entirety of our spiraling climate meltdown. From this point of view, almost anything is better. We need to ditch coal and oil ASAP, no matter what it takes. At the same time, we should be taking a long look at the problems with batteries—battery fires, the use of child labor to mine rare minerals, etc.—so they don\'t become yet another disaster. Lithium-ion batteries, especially those powering most e-bikes and scooters, need to improve drastically. In addition to long charging times, the most pressing concern is catching fire. Lithium-ion batteries have already sparked 22 fires that caused 36 injuries and two deaths in New York City this year, Charlie Welch, CEO and co-founder of ZapBatt, told Lifewire via email. EV Battery Life Batteries are fueling EV growth, from giant SUVs to humble electric bikes. We focus on the good aspects: that they can be recharged, there are no local emissions, electric motors are silent, etc. But we also ignore the problems. First, producing batteries has a significant environmental and human impact. Until a battery can be made sustainably from both a human and environmental perspective, the growth of battery use won\'t be sustainable. Too commonly, batteries are made with cobalt, which is a highly volatile and unsustainable mineral to source. There are several cobalt mines in Africa, particularly in the Congo, where child labor is all too common, Ashish Gadnis, CEO of sustainable-sourcing company BanQu told Lifewire via email. And even after manufacturing, the lifecycle of a battery is shorter than you might expect. Because many e-bike and scooter OEMs use cheaper batteries with shorter life cycles, there is unfortunately a growing mountain of e-waste. With micro-mobility operators swapping a tsunami of conventional lithium-ion batteries on e-bikes and e-scooters, and with few recycling options available at present, we are well on our way to building a massive battery graveyard and squandering the rare earth minerals used to manufacture them, says ZappBat\'s Welch. EV Battery Recycling Then, too, recycling itself has an impact. Oftentimes, we think that encouraging recycling is the catch-all solution to making the material more sustainable. But unfortunately, it isn\'t. Recycling programs are often happening at these very mines where child labor is rampant. So until a battery can be made sustainably from both a human and environmental perspective, the growth of battery use won\'t be sustainable, says Gadnis A worker in protective clothing loading vehicle batteries into a bin at a recycling plant. Monty Rakusen / Getty Images And that\'s if you can even recycle them. At the end of their lives, batteries can become pretty toxic. Many batteries and solar panel parts are not recyclable, which obviously increases our waste generation. Improperly disposed [of] batteries can also cause soil, water, and air pollution, Caio Bersot, energy analyst at EnergyRates.ca, told Lifewire via email. Alternatives Like Hydrogen Fuel Cells One other option is hydrogen. It\'s not perfect, of course, and it would require a distribution network similar in principle to that of gasoline rather than using our existing electricity grid. But the advantage is that refueling can be faster than charging a car (you can fill up in just four minutes), and the car still runs on electricity and produces only water as waste. Hydrogen fuel cells, although a bit more expensive than electric vehicles, have a smaller impact on the environment as they only emit water when powered with hydrogen. However, all vehicles, regardless of how they are powered, will require multiple resources, both natural and manufactured, says Bersot. Closeup on the back of a car that has an emblem that reads Hydrogen Fuel Cell. gchutka / Getty Images But hydrogen is also—like batteries— less energy dense than gas, so you need to carry more of it and store it at high pressure. The real problem is that we have built some societies around individual vehicles for both extended and short-distance use. Those vehicles are far too big, a hangover from the plentiful energy of cheap gasoline. Long-distance journeys are best made on electric trains that don\'t run on batteries, while shorter trips can be made by bike or public city transport—again, all of which can be battery-free.</string>
    <string name="maruti_suzuki_has_said_that_it_has_secured_a_19_percent_market_share_in_the_rs_10_lakh_to_rs_20_lakh_vehicle_category_in_fy2022_23_making_it_the_number_one_player_in_this_segment_this_puts_maruti_ahead_of_its_arch_rivals_like_hyundai_india_the_company_also_said_that_its_market_share_has_risen_to_22_percent_in_the_first_quarter_of_fy24_april_june_2023_thanks_to_more_demand_for_its_premium_suvs_maruti_currently_has_61_percent_market_share_in_the_sub_rs_10_lakh_category_market_share_in_rs_10_lakh_20_lakh_segment_quadrupled_in_last_few_years_maruti_s_nexa_outlets_sold_3_7_lakh_units_in_fy23_maruti_suzuki_has_over_2_lakh_pending_suv_orders_the_brand_has_traditionally_been_a_small_car_specialist_and_has_over_61_percent_segment_share_in_the_sub_rs_10_lakh_category_speaking_on_the_sidelines_of_the_invicto_s_launch_event_last_week_shashank_srivastava_executive_director_of_sales_marketing_at_maruti_suzuki_india_told_our_sister_publication_autocar_professional_whichever_segment_maruti_suzuki_enters_into_it_is_able_to_create_a_mark_only_the_types_of_products_and_the_consumers_change_the_company_understands_the_indian_consumers_well_and_is_able_to_break_into_a_fresh_and_new_customer_base_for_invicto_a_vehicle_priced_between_rs_25_lakh_and_rs_30_lakh_maruti_suzuki_was_able_to_gather_a_booking_of_over_6_800_units_in_the_last_few_weeks_the_company_is_sitting_on_an_order_book_of_over_2_lakh_suvs_predominantly_in_the_rs_10_lakh_20_lakh_bracket_its_market_share_in_this_price_segment_has_quadrupled_in_the_last_few_years_from_4_5_percent_to_20_22_percent_and_the_big_factor_behind_this_is_its_range_of_new_suvs_and_mpvs_that_it_has_introduced_since_2018_not_surprisingly_maruti_suzuki_is_already_the_second_largest_player_in_the_fast_growing_suv_space_just_a_few_hundred_units_behind_mahindra_mahindra_multiple_factors_pushing_the_shift_towards_higher_priced_vehicles_the_shift_towards_higher_priced_cars_has_been_driven_by_rising_commodity_costs_road_taxes_insurance_pay_out_and_increased_features_and_hence_the_average_price_of_cars_sold_in_india_has_breached_rs_9_lakh_10_lakh_from_an_average_of_about_rs_6_lakh_7_lakh_just_three_to_five_years_ago_it_is_a_fallacy_or_a_myth_that_maruti_can_t_sell_premium_cars_or_suvs_or_upgraders_prefer_other_brands_nexa_our_premium_channel_is_set_to_be_the_second_biggest_automotive_retailer_after_arena_on_a_base_of_3_7_lakh_units_in_fy23_we_have_so_far_grown_over_70_percent_and_the_sales_from_nexa_are_likely_to_cross_about_half_a_million_units_underscored_srivastava_regarding_the_rs_20_lakh_to_rs_30_lakh_segment_where_the_invicto_mpv_is_positioned_srivastava_said_the_segment_accounts_for_5_8_percent_of_the_indian_passenger_vehicle_market_and_a_majority_of_these_customers_are_not_first_time_car_buyers_naturally_given_the_higher_price_tag_the_share_of_first_time_car_buyers_is_very_small_in_this_segment_but_there_is_a_big_chunk_of_replacement_buyers_approximately_4_5_million_suvs_are_likely_to_be_sold_in_india_between_2020_to_2027_and_experts_reckon_that_this_upgraded_space_of_rs_20_lakh_to_rs_30_lakh_will_turn_out_to_be_the_new_battleground_for_automakers_to_fight_for_in_the_next_five_years"><![CDATA[Maruti Suzuki has said that it has secured a 19 percent market share in the Rs 10 lakh to Rs 20 lakh vehicle category in FY2022-\'23, making it the number one player in this segment. This puts Maruti ahead of its arch rivals like Hyundai India. The company also said that its market share has risen to 22 percent in the first quarter of FY24 (April-June 2023), thanks to more demand for its premium SUVs. Maruti currently has 61 percent market share in the sub-Rs 10 lakh category Market share in Rs 10 lakh-20 lakh segment quadrupled in last few years Maruti\'s Nexa outlets sold 3.7 lakh units in FY23 Maruti Suzuki has over 2 lakh pending SUV orders The brand has traditionally been a small car specialist, and has over 61 percent segment share in the sub-Rs 10 lakh category. Speaking on the sidelines of the Invicto\'s launch event last week, Shashank Srivastava, executive director of Sales & Marketing at Maruti Suzuki India, told our sister publication Autocar Professional, Whichever segment Maruti Suzuki enters into, it is able to create a mark, only the types of products and the consumers change. The company understands the Indian consumers well, and is able to break into a fresh and new customer base. For Invicto – a vehicle priced between Rs 25 lakh and Rs 30 lakh – Maruti Suzuki was able to gather a booking of over 6,800 units in the last few weeks. The company is sitting on an order book of over 2 lakh SUVs, predominantly in the Rs 10 lakh-20 lakh bracket. Its market share in this price segment has quadrupled in the last few years from 4-5 percent to 20-22 percent, and the big factor behind this is its range of new SUVs and MPVs that it has introduced since 2018. Not surprisingly, Maruti Suzuki is already the second largest player in the fast-growing SUV space, just a few hundred units behind Mahindra & Mahindra. Multiple factors pushing the shift towards higher-priced vehicles The shift towards higher-priced cars has been driven by rising commodity costs, road taxes, insurance pay out and increased features, and hence the average price of cars sold in India has breached Rs 9 lakh-10 lakh from an average of about Rs 6 lakh-7 lakh just three to five years ago. It is a fallacy or a myth that Maruti can\'t sell premium cars or SUVs or upgraders prefer other brands. Nexa, our premium channel, is set to be the second biggest automotive retailer [after Arena]. On a base of 3.7 lakh units in FY23, we have so far grown over 70 percent and the sales from Nexa are likely to cross about half a million units,” underscored Srivastava. Regarding the Rs 20 lakh to Rs 30 lakh segment where the Invicto MPV is positioned, Srivastava said the segment accounts for 5-8 percent of the Indian passenger vehicle market and a majority of these customers are not first-time car buyers. Naturally, given the higher price tag, the share of first-time car buyers is very small in this segment, but there is a big chunk of replacement buyers. Approximately 4-5 million SUVs are likely to be sold in India between 2020 to 2027, and experts reckon that this upgraded space of Rs 20 lakh to Rs 30 lakh will turn out to be the new battleground for automakers to fight for in the next five years.]]></string>
    <string name="load_more_cars">Load More cars</string>
    <string name="rs_15_00_15_00_lakh">Rs. 15.00 - 15.00 Lakh</string>
    <string name="mahindra_xuv700">Mahindra XUV700</string>
    <string name="rs_5_lakh">Rs.5. Lakh*</string>
</resources>